Finding Aid for Bradley v. Milliken case files, 1962-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Bradley v. Milliken case files
  - Correspondence
    - Citizens: letters to and from individuals, groups, and municipalities expressing support or opposition to developments in Milliken v. Bradley
      - 1970 (Box 11)
        (11-27)
      - 1971, 2 folders (Box 11)
        (11-28; 11-29)
      - 1972, 4 folders (Box 12)
        (12-1, etc.-12-4)
    - News media inquiries and judicial correspondence regarding interviews 1971-1974 (Box 12)
      (12-5)
    - Invitations for speaking engagements 1971-1974 (Box 12)
      (12-6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Bulletins, newsletters, and press releases related to Bradley v. Milliken, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
      (12-7)
    - Relevant court cases: motions, decisions, and reviews 1971-1973 (Box 12)
      (12-8)
    - Reports
      - "Suggested Guidelines for Providing for the Maximal Education of Children of all Races and Creeds in the Schools of Michigan" (MI Department of Public Instruction) 1964 (Box 12)
        (12-9)
      - "The Face of Detroit: a Spatial Analysis" (Robert Sinclair, WSU) 1970 (Box 12)
        (12-10)
      - "Racial-Ethnic Distribution of Students and Employees in the Detroit Public Schools" (Division of School-Community Relations), October 1971 (Box 12)
        (12-11)
      - "Comments on the Controversy over School Busing" (NAACP Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc.) May 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-12)
      - "Your Child and Busing" (U.S. Commission on Civil Rights) May 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-13)
      - "ACLU Annual Report" June 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-14)
      - "School Desegregation: Legal Precedents, Methods, Effects" (League of Women Voters of the Detroit Metropolitan Area) December 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-15)
    - Journals, magazines and newsletters related to the topic of desegregation and Milliken v. Bradley
      - Atlantic Monthly, March 1973 (Box 12)
        (12-16)
      - The Crisis, March 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-17)
      - Inequality in Education (Harvard Center for Law and Education), March 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-18)
      - Integrated Education: a Report on Race and Schools, November-December 1971 (Box 12)
        (12-19)
      - Intellectual Digest, June 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-20)
      - Judicature, April 1971 (Box 12)
        (12-21)
      - National Clearinghouse for Legal Services: Clearinghouse Review, January 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-22)
      - Law Quadrangle Notes (University of Michigan Law School), 1973 (Box 12)
        (12-23)
      - Newsweek, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
        (12-24)
      - Notre Dame Magazine, February 1973 (Box 12)
        (12-25)
      - Psychology Today, February 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-26)
      - Race Relations Reporter, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
        (12-27)
      - Ripon Forum, April 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-28)
      - Saturday Review, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
        (12-29)
      - Teacher's Voice (Michigan Education Association), February 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-30)
      - Time, 1971 (Box 12)
        (12-31)
      - University of Chicago Law Review, 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-32)
      - US News and World Report, 1971 (Box 12)
        (12-33)
      - Wayne State University Alumni News, January 1972 (Box 12)
        (12-34)
    - ACLU Eleventh Anniversary Dinner Program (honoring Charles Kaufman, Damon Keith, and Stephen Roth) February 1973 (Box 12)
      (12-35)
    - Other 1970-1971 (Box 12)
      (12-36)